Guide to the Federal Theatre Project photograph collection, 1936-1939
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
Federal Theatre Project photograph collection
1936-1939
C0205
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
47.0 linear feet (112 boxes)
This collection consists of graphic materials relating to Federal Theatre Project productions from 1936 to 1939 across the United States, with the majority from New York City and Roslyn, New York, San Diego and San Francisco, California, and Chicago, Illinois. The collection is mostly comprised of black and white photographs ranging in size from 4x5 to 11x14 and duplicate prints, as well as a few negatives.
Federal Theatre Project (U.S.)
Scope and Content
This collection consists of graphic materials relating to Federal Theatre Project productions from 1936 to 1939 across the United States, with the majority from New York City and Roslyn, New York, San Diego and San Francisco, California, and Chicago, Illinois. The collection is mostly comprised of black and white photographs ranging in size from 4x5 to 11x14 and duplicate prints, as well as a few negatives.
Series one is titled Production Photographs. The series is comprised of photographs and negatives relating to productions, the majority of which are scene shots and portraits of employees, but the series also includes portraits of well-known figures of the day such as Eleanor Roosevelt and the Scottsboro Boys, and prints of audiences, caravan theater, children's theater, circus, community theater presentation, marionette construction, office personnel, posters, radio performances, rehearsals, sets, behind-the-scenes techniques, vaudeville, and workshops. Included are scene and stage production shots from living newspaper productions, such as "Triple-A Plowed Under," "Injunction Granted," "1935," "One-Third of a Nation," "Power," and "Spirochete," as well as from the Negro, Yiddish, and Radio units. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 1 to 82. It is arranged alphabetically by production title, state and city; by surname; or by subject. Some of the subjects included are audience, circus, dance, marionette, publicity, set, technical, theatres, and workshops. Duplicates can be found both within folders and across folders (more than one folder with the same heading); oversize duplicates are included in series two.
Series two is titled Oversize Production Photographs. The series is comprised of photographs relating to productions, including scene shots, stage and set shots, and portraits. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 83 to 88. The series is arranged alphabetically by production title, state and city, or by subject. This series includes oversize duplicates from photographs contained in series one and series three.
Series three is titled Portraits. The series is comprised of headshots and portraits of actors, actresses, and directors involved in Federal Theatre productions. The series includes portraits of unidentified actors and actresses from various plays, such as "It Can't Happen Here," "No More Peace," "Power," "Sing for Your Supper," "Processional," etc. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 88 to 93. The series is arranged alphabetically by surname. Duplicates can be found both within folders and across folders (more than one folder with the same heading); oversize duplicates are included in series two.
Series four is titled Microfiche. The series contains microfiche featuring a variety of subjects that are related to the Federal Theater Project. Each file contains at least one negative and one positive of each subject with most of the files having duplicates. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 95 to 104. It is arranged alphabetically by production title, by surname, or by subject. Some of the subjects included are actors, actresses, authors, audience, circus, dance, directors, employees, marionette, publicity, scenes, set, technical, theatres, and workshops.
Series five is titled Printing Materials. This series is split into three subseries: Zinc Plates and Mats, Woodblocks, and Mimeographs.This series contains zinc plates, mats, mimeographs and woodblocks that were used in the production of publications for the Federal Theater Project. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 105 to 112. The series is arranged alphabetically starting with productions and then going into portraits.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Library of Congress, National Archives and Records Administration, and acquired through purchase.
Alternative Form Available
The costumes and set designs are also available as a series in the. There are photographs from this collection and other FTP collections in the There are also 35 mm microfiche negatives made from original Federal Theatre Project photographs in the early 1980s.
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives holds the Federal Theatre Project collection, which includes numerous personal and organizational records as well as oral histories.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series. Series one is arranged alphabetically by production title, state and city; by surname; or by subject. Series two is arranged alphabetically by production title, state and city, or by subject. Series three is arranged alphabetically by surname.
Series 1: Production Photographs, 1936-1939
Series 2: Oversize Production Photographs,1936-1939
Series 3: Portraits, 1936-1939
Series 4: Microfiche, 1936-1939
Series 5: Printing Materials, 1936-1939
Historical Note
Organized in 1935, The Federal Theatre Project flourished as the first and only federally sponsored and subsidized theater program in the United States until its end in 1939. The FTP was a division of the Works Progress Administration (WPA), which provided employment for large numbers of artists, writers, and performers during the Great Depression (1929-1939). Directed by Hallie Flanagan (1880-1969), the FTP provided employment for theatrical professionals throughout the United States during the Great Depression. Actors, playwrights, scene designers and builders, seamstresses, lighting experts, ushers, box-office men, and stagehands all found employment through the FTP.
Like many New Deal programs implemented by President Franklin D. Roosevelt, the Federal Theatre Project was intended not only to benefit its participants, but also to enrich the condition of the nation. Theater was a distinguished part of American popular culture, but the economic downturn of the Depression had bankrupted the entire theater industry. As the theater houses closed down, the nation was left without an outlet for theatrical creativity. According to Hallie Flanagan, this hurt the nation as much as it hurt the theater industry - indeed, the nation was their audience and the theater could provide entertaining distractions from the effects of Depression as well as offer commentary on present conditions.
But it was not enough to simply return to the pre-Depression concept of theater. In the first meeting with her staff Flanagan expressed her willingness to follow Roosevelt's experimental approach to public policy: "In a changing world, a world of experiment, the stage too must experiment - with ideas, with the psychological relationship of men and women, with color and light.... The theatre must grow up."
Flanagan pursued her ideal of developing the relationship between the Federal Theatre and the federal government: "Any theatre sponsored by the government of the United States should do no plays of a cheap, trivial, outworn or vulgar nature, but only such plays as the Government can stand proudly behind in a planned theatrical program, national in scope, regional in emphasis, and American in democratic attitude." To Flanagan, it was imperative that this new theater should be progressive and experimental, yet within a patriotic and informative framework.
The productions that best embodied Flanagan's views on theater were the Living Newspapers. These hard-hitting, poignant plays dealt with contemporary factual material, dramatizing issues such as housing, agriculture, labor, and destitution. Always ending on an upbeat note, Living Newspapers underscored the importance of hard work and morality in overcoming difficult times. Living Newspaper titles include: Triple A Plowed Under, Injunction Granted, One Third of a Nation, and Spirochete.
The Federal Theatre was noted for employing black Americans at a time when the Federal Government did not actively protect the rights of minorities. The "Negro Theater" (as it was called in the 1930s) was an established industry before the Depression, and it greatly contributed to the success of the Federal Theatre Project. Some of the most spectacular productions were put on by black theater professionals, for example: Macbeth, Haiti, Turpentine, Run Little Chillun, and The Trial of Dr. Beck.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Federal Theatre Project (U.S.); Actors--Photographs.; Theatre--New York--New York.
Document Types:
Negatives.; Photographs.; Portraits.
Contents List
- Series 1: Production Photographs, 1936-1939; (84 boxes)
  This series consists of photographs and negatives relating to productions, the majority of which are scene shots and portraits of employees, but the series also includes portraits of well-known figures of the day such as Eleanor Roosevelt and the Scottsboro Boys, and prints of audiences, caravan theater, children's theater, circus, community theater presentation, marionette construction, office personnel, posters, radio performances, rehearsals, sets, behind-the-scenes techniques, vaudeville, and workshops. Included are scene and stage production shots from living newspaper productions, such as "Triple-A Plowed Under," "Injunction Granted," "1935," "One-Third of a Nation," "Power," and "Spirochete," as well as from the Negro, Yiddish, and Radio units. The series is dated from 1936 to 1939 and is contained in boxes 1 to 82. It is arranged alphabetically by production title, state and city; by surname; or by subject. Some of the subjects included are audience, circus, dance, marionette, publicity, set, technical, theatres, and workshops. Duplicates are included within this series; oversize duplicates are included in series two.
  - 9 Pine Street (Roslyn, New York), April 21, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 9 Pine Street (Roslyn, New York), 1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 9 Pine Street (Roslyn, New York), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 9 Pine Street (Roslyn, New York), April 20, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 9 Pine Street -- Outside of Theatre, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 200 Were Chosen (Peoria, Illinois), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1935 -- A Living Newspaper (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1935 -- A Living Newspaper (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1935, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Abraham Lincoln, The Great Commoner (Peoria, Illinois), August 28, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Accent on Youth (San Diego, California), October 18 - November 10, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Accent on Youth (Boston, Massachusetts), March 3, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adding Machine (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adding Machine (Denver, Colorado), February 26, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adelante (New York City, New York), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adelante (New York City, New York), 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - African Dancers -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Afrique -- Marionette (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - After Dark (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ah, Wilderness (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Ah, Wilderness production photograph, 1938
  - Ah, Wilderness (San Diego, California), January 24, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ah, Wilderness (San Diego, California), January 24, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Ah, Wilderness production photograph, January 24, 1938
  - Ah, Wilderness (San Diego, California), January 24, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ah, Wilderness (Peoria, Illinois), November 26, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ah, Wilderness (Boston, Massachusetts), January 19, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ah, Wilderness (New Orleans, Louisiana), June 3, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Ah, Wilderness production photograph, June 3, 1938
    - Ah, Wilderness production photograph, June 3, 1938
    - Ah, Wilderness production photograph, June 3, 1938
  - Ah, Wilderness (New Orleans, Louisiana), June 3, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ah, Wilderness (Seattle, Washington), April 1, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ah, Wilderness (Seattle, Washington), April 1, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ah, Wilderness, October 14, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Aladdin -- Set photographs, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Aladdin (Los Angeles, California), March 5 - 11, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Aladdin (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Aladdin -- Children's Theater, September 25, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Alice In Wonderland (San Diego, California), December 31, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Alice In Wonderland (San Diego, California), December 21 - 31, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Alice In Wonderland -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), June 15, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Alice In Wonderland -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), June 15, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alice In Wonderland (New York City, New York), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alice In Wonderland, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alien Corn (Los Angeles, California), October 12, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alien Corn (Los Angeles, California), September 9 - October 12, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alien Corn (San Francisco, California), August 20, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alien Corn (San Francisco, California), August 20, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alison's House (Los Angeles, California), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alison's House -- Set, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - All American Minstrels (New York City, New York), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - All American Minstrels (New York City, New York), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Altars of Steel (Miami, Florida), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Altars of Steel (Miami, Florida and Atlanta, Georgia), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Altars of Steel (Miami, Florida), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Altars of Steel (Atlanta, Georgia), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Altars of Steel (Atlanta, Georgia), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Altars of Steel (Atlanta, Georgia), 1936 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Amazing Dr. Clitterhouse (Los Angeles, California), April 21, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Amazing Dr. Clitterhouse (San Francisco, California), February 25, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Amazing Dr. Clitterhouse (San Francisco, California), February 25, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Amazing Dr. Clitterhouse (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Amazing Dr. Clitterhouse (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - America Sings (Arkansas), 1930s (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - America Sings (Arkansas), 1930s (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Family Robinson, April 26, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - American Family Robinson -- Set photographs, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - American Holiday (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - American Wing (Boston, Massachusetts), March 17, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American Wing (Springfield, Massachusetts), August 11, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Los Angeles, California), December 16, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Denver, Colorado), January 23, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Denver, Colorado and Washington), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Atlanta, Georgia), March 17, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Androcles and the Lion (New York, Colorado, California, Washington), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Androcles and the Lion (Seattle, Washington), November 4, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Animal Kingdom (San Francisco, California), October 15 - 17, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Animal Kingdom (San Francisco, California), October 15 - 17, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Animal Kingdom (San Francisco, California), October 17, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Animal Kingdom (Denver, Colorado), April 22, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Animal Kingdom (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Animal Kingdom (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Anna Christie (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Anna Christie (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Anna Christie (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Anna Christie (San Diego, California), September 22 - 29, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Anna Christie (Denver, Colorado), January 31, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Anna Christie (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Another Language (San Diego, California), July 6, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Another Language (San Diego, California), July 6, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Another Language (San Diego, California), July 6, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Another Language (San Diego, California), July 6, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Another Language (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Another Language (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Anthony and Anna (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Anthony and Cleopatra (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Are You Listening -- Vaudeville (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Are You Listening -- Vaudeville (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Arms and the Man (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Arms and the Man (San Diego, California), October 25 - 27, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Arms and the Man (Des Moines, Iowa), December 8, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Arms and the Man (Boston, Massachusetts), November 19, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Arms and the Man -- Set photographs, October 25 - 27, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Around the Corner (Peoria, Illinois), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Around the World in 80 Days (Newark, New Jersey), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Around the World in 80 Days (Newark, New Jersey), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Art and Mrs. Bottle (New Orleans, Louisiana), May 6, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - As Husbands Go (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - As You Like It -- SERA (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - As You Like It (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - As You Like It (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Ask Dad (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ask Dad (New York City, New York), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Attention Please (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Attention Please (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Audience, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Audience, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Audience (New York City), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Audience -- Adrienne Marlowe for Portable Theatre, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Audience -- Photograph of Blackstone Theatre, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Audience (Blue Mound, Illinois), 1930s (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Audience -- Caravan Unit Productions, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Audience -- Caravan Theatre, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Audience -- Children, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Audience -- Children Standing, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Audience (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Audience -- Children's Theatre (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Audience -- Circus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Audience -- Circus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Audience -- Circus, July 8, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Audience -- Circus, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Audience -- Eleanor Roosevelt, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Audience -- Eleanor Roosevelt, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Audience -- The Emperor's New Clothes, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Audience -- The Emperor's New Clothes, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Audience -- The Emperor's New Clothes, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Audience -- Federal Theatre Project of Maine (Dry Mills, Maine), July 20, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Audience -- Flotilla of Faith, May 10, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Audience -- Folder IV, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Audience -- Folder IV, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Audience -- Help Yourself, July 19, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Audience -- Help Yourself -- CCC Camp, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Audience -- House that Jack's Building, May 13, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Audience -- House that Jack's Building, May 13, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Audience -- Iolanthe, June 14, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Audience -- Iolanthe, June 14, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Audience -- Interior view of tent (Springfield, Illinois), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Audience -- It Can't Happen Here, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Audience -- It Can't Happen Here -- Caravan Unit, Owl's Head Park, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Audience -- It Can't Happen Here, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Audience -- It Can't Happen Here, June 1, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Audience -- Life of Stephen Foster (Sloan, New York), August 10, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Audience -- Little Jesse James, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Audience -- Little Jesse James, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Audience -- Marionette Division, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Audience -- May Festival, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Audience -- May Festival, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Audience -- Midsummer Night's Dream (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Audience -- Midsummer Night's Dream, June 4, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Audience -- Midsummer Night's Dream, June 1937 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Audience -- Midsummer Night's Dream, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Audience -- Noah -- Negro, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Audience (Oklahoma City, Oklahoma and Milwaukee, Wisconsin), 1930s (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Audience -- Outside Theatre, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Audience -- Outside Theatre, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Audience -- Outdoor Audience Shots, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Audience -- Outdoor ground shots of audience, 1930s (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Audience -- Pinocchio, May 1939 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Audience -- Pinocchio -- Joe Penner Theatre Party, December 4, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Audience -- Pirates Ahoy, March 4, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Audience -- Pittsburgh Unit -- Government and Postal Employees Picnic (Jacktown, Pennsylvania), September 26 - 28, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Audience -- Audience shots with police officers, 1930s (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Audience -- Portable Theatre, 1930s (Box 7, Folder 4)